Saved .pkl or .joblib models, final figures, and performance reports.


scatterplotbirthrate20102020.PNG : Scatter plot of birth rate in 2010 vs. 2020. High persistence (Pearson r = 0.896) demonstrates lagged birth rate is a valid predictor.
2529dem2010heatmap.PNG : Heat map shows negative correlation with White female share (25-29) but positive with Black and Hispanic female share (25 -29).
birthrate2020histogram.PNG : Histogram shows unimodal, right-skewed distribution of 2020 birth rate with a few high- and low-fertility outliers.